i have a crush on this guy right now
who's totally marriage material because
he's married
you're so hot i do in front of my
grandparents yeah you should be ashamed
of yourself like i love that thank you
very much
[Applause]
so i remember i wanted to try waxing so
i was like oh i'll just go to walgreens
and get a kit and do it myself
i like arts and crafts
and i don't like arts and crafts i've
never finished a scrapbook in my life
didn't finish this one either i didn't
get past the second page if you know
what i'm saying
i don't know what i'm saying no it was
the worst they give you microwavable wax
but every microwave is different i just
put it in and pressed popcorn i didn't
know
[Music]
oh god i uh i burnt myself i scolded my
not scalded i always
yeah at school i was like um
yeah i really thought it was i scalded
myself and i only got two strips in and
then i gave up
and i was like well i guess this is my
new look
looks like a pause button but you know
what
metaphor for my sex life now
[Music]
putting this on pause
i was clever with it i called it the
patch adams uh
because when i put a clown nose on it it
made sick kids laugh so that's why i
called it that it was like a fun day of
volunteering that i did so
thank you
i don't know what to do down there
anymore
it's like i um i used to take pictures
um because my my ex-boyfriend asked me
to send naked photos and i was smart i
didn't put my face in it
uh mostly because that's how he asked
for them but also because
that's the smart way to do it but it's
hard to make that picture look sexy
you know you're just laying on a bed you
crop off your head it just looks like a
crime scene photo like it's not
a good look it was the worst
eventually he was just like stop sending
me these headless horse woman photos i
don't need them in my life
or my phone so then i remember i got a
text
once that was like synthetics
at like 4 a.m and i was like gross
no but then he had a really good
argument for why i should
because he was like come on that was it
but i was like
wow okay
i'll fax them over promptly
i am i miss i miss sex
i'm gonna do it again someday i gotta
get better at masturbating in the
meantime
i'm terrible at it i don't know what i'm
doing
it's um most the time i just find an
itch and i scratch and i'm like yes am i
done
like that felt great but i'm not
done then i just fake an orgasm by
myself
just to get it over with
oh god i don't know what to do
i um i try to fantasize i try to watch
like i'm not into porn
but i'll try to like find my porn like a
good john mayer clip on youtube or
something and i
put that on mute and then i uh
yeah well i like his music it's just for
me it's about his face because you can't
sit on a voice so that's just how i feel
about
john mayer um
but i can't it's like because then i'm
like he's a celebrity you can't have
them that's stupid so i try to fantasize
about like maybe someone in my life and
i'm like
oh like maybe like i have a crush on
this guy right now who's totally
marriage material because he's married
but um that's the worst to fantasize
about because then i'm just touching
myself to his wife and kids dying and
that's never good it's
uh i mean i do it in a jet ski accident
so it's kind of sexy
but yeah they have a lot of fun up until
that bridge but that bridge just
comes out of nowhere and she shouldn't
have been drunk jet skiing though that's
kind of on her
thank you thank you so much
so yeah i'm not looking for i'm looking
forward to having sex again but sober
sex is gonna be weird cause i'm gonna be
um
conscious for when you guys uh that's
always frightening
do you guys know that you turn into
demons when you are you aware of that
is that a thing that you are conscious
of
it scared me the first time it happened
a lot
i did not see it because you're so sweet
to us up until that moment it's just
like oh baby that's just
like whoa where's scott what did you do
with scott
it's horrifying
[Music]
it's so scary and then it gets then you
call
then it's just you collapse on us
and it gets really quiet i'm like the
beast is dead
i killed him but then you reanimate back
into your old cell you're like hey
i'm like i've seen the real you get off
so scary but it's what you do and it's
weird when you think about it because
all of us we're all here right now
like living right now because some dude
once went like
isn't that weird have you ever thought
about that
all of us because some dude i know
and by some dude i mean your father
he thinks i'm like you know just this
i'm being this version of a girl that
he's gonna fall in love with like i'm
clean
and and nice and i've never done anal
like i'm just like this pure
and i have uh not like a ton but like he
asked me if i've done it and of course i
said no i'm not gonna be like yeah i'm a
huge butt
i'm not gonna like you have to say
never done it and i know a lot of people
in here are like no i would never do it
because i used to be that way
and then i did coke and
you are missing out you should do it but
if you don't want to do it girls
instead of being like no it's gross i
think you should go the other way and
like seem
super into it like too into it
that's the that's that's just like yeah
we should
and i think i would love it because i
like love pooping
so if you say it that way like really
sell it i know it's gross but be like i
love it going out so i'll probably love
it going in like
get in there cowboy call him cowboy just
freak him out
he'll leave you so you'll never have to
do it
i take the pill um when i remember so
that's not how you're supposed to take
it
a lot my friend was like why don't you
do it like a diaphragm
and i'm like are you from the 80s like
what's going on
i didn't really do my research on the
diaphragm i should have asked my grandma
about it but
she uses a pull out method so
i've always heard about the diaphragm on
like old episodes of seinfeld and
antiques roadshow
and i'd never seen one
so i google-imaged it and um the image
that came up i don't know if you guys
have seen a diaphragm but they look
exactly that that toy we used to get as
kids
that little rubber thing you flip then
you like set it on something and you
wait
and then it like pops i don't even know
what those are called
i think they're diaphragms guys yeah i
don't know how you put them in
that seems weird maybe you would just
flip it
and then set it down and then like hover
over
it and like wait david spade
the host with the most step stools in
your apartment
david you seriously influenced so many
female comics haircuts
rob riggle i want to thank you so much
for fighting the war against terrorism
and subtlety
jimmy a car is what ralph macchio has to
do to find a place to sleep every night
jewel is here or as i call her trailer
swift
jewel i do not want to bad matthew since
god already did
no
[Applause]
i think your smile is cute i feel like
your teeth are like the spice girls you
know they're all different colors and
they're like doing their own things
so that's fun
[Applause]
peyton manning is here that's not for
you guys that's for him peyton you're
here right now you've had a lot of
concussions
you're here don't murder your wife
i i don't know much about football but i
love peyton
uh in commercials you're like you're so
good at him like legitimately i'd say
you're the greatest of all time i'd say
like
you're like the tom brady of being in
commercials you know like
the greatest like he's the greatest
right so
and without furor adieu and coulter
oh and what's it like to be like a
real-life
super villain you know like i'd ask you
how you sleep at night but i'd
assume just upside down in a robe of 101
dalmatians
ann coulter has written 11 books 12 if
you count mein kampf
yes anne's been called
things like a racist anti-semitic
homophobic a white supremacist and
that's just while getting plowed by bill
maher
the only person you will ever make happy
is the mexican who digs your grave
[Applause]
rob lowe
rob defies age restrictions
[Applause]
you really you're you're adonis
look at you
you look like you're sculpted god i had
such a crush on you when i was a little
girl
if only i'd known that's when i had my
best shot
thank you so much i am like obsessed
with talking about sex i
apologize if it's not your thing but
like come on it's like so fun
and uh like we're all having sex but we
don't really like talk about it like
we'll be like oh yeah i've had sex
before like we'll admit that but we
won't be like oh yeah i've been like
but that's like what you look like no
one admits that they're like no i look
cooler
no you don't you're just like like this
it's just a bunch of like skin like
shaking it's so gross
and you all look like it we all do but
like the only thing that like
differentiates us is like we put on
clothes and we're like nope i've never
done that what's going like
as soon as you're not naked you can be
like no i don't do that what are you
talking about i'm a princess
like that's what's separating us it's
just clothes like you can give like a
sloppy blow job and put on like
some jeans and a tank top and be like
i've never sucked in my life what are
you talking about
[Music]
nope not me and it's like yes you have
if you weren't a tank top male or female
you suck something
like that's just a fact of tank tops i
think
yeah pregnant women are my favorite
because you're like
i know you doing it like
hey you got stuffed you got stuff like
you know it
and uh and then you oh you can find out
like exactly when
she had sex like all you have to do is
ask like whenever you do or pretend you
care or whatever
and then you just do some light math and
you count back nine months and you're
like july
you were just like oh like in july you
were getting it
you love it yeah
you should be ashamed of yourself like i
love that
that's the thing about being pregnant
like you if you tell your parents you're
pregnant like you're pretty much like
dad chris inside me come here
i kept it in like this
joseph gordon love it everyone
he's so cute so adorable i bet you eat
but only with the crust cut off
first
isn't that his luck speaking of krusty
i'll get to you in a second sybil
i
am
i know i know
martha stewart thank you for being here
seriously and congratulations on getting
that thai soccer team out of your vagina
and into your sweatshops
that's where they are now
surprisingly martha said that prison
food wasn't that bad
just you know as long as it was
clean-shaven so
she loves attention to detail
is she laughing i'm terrified of her
no i at my honestly martha i'm a huge
fan and my mom is an even bigger fan my
mom has learned everything from martha
stewart about cooking and cleaning and
withholding affection
so it's close to my heart
sybil's gorgeous i'm like honored to
meet her and um
and to her resume is insane like if you
look at it it's just like model
actor singer you name it she's it
[Laughter]
i wish it wasn't true i don't know any
of these people
sybil why am i here
ugh literally you have like no friends
um
it's truly so cool to be sharing the
stage with these badass women
sybil shepherd martha stewart margaret
cho
i'm sorry dawn marrera i'm sorry
i thought that was
dumb a rare i know you sleepy potato
tom i love you but how did you have a
stroke on both sides of your face
explain that i don't get it
dennis rodman what's up
dennis rodman i first met dennis just
earlier tonight when he tried to sell me
incense on the sidewalk
i don't want any okay edward norton is
here
hey buddy ed looks to me like if a
marionette became a boy and then that
boy
became an right
he was so hot in fight club right
when he was brad pitt that was nuts
now let's get too
bruce yes this is honestly a real
uh a big personal moment for me to be
here roasting my dead cousin's second
favorite action star
i know you obviously as the star of
every dvd
you kind of just find on the street
obviously you had an amazing action film
career until jason statham started
balding
i'm just not familiar with action movies
i don't know i've never
seen a single one of your films
consensually
like it's always what some guy puts on
while he's trying to finger me on his
roommate's couch you know what i'm
saying
maybe i didn't understand the fifth
element and it wasn't because i'm a dumb
girl but because it's hard to follow
that plot when you're fighting off a
roofie and there's a knuckle inside you
you know just me
oh i love the sixth sense though i loved
and the ending when the guy came in my
eye and i didn't have to watch the rest
of it that was great
a lot of people don't know that bruce is
a very talented musician
because he isn't
bruce has also been very active with the
make-a-wish foundation which is where
they make sick kids meet you so dying
doesn't seem so terrible
so cool bruce in all honesty
thank you for having me here you're
really cool you're
so hot and this is a special night you
really are
it's a special night obviously your
families your daughters must be so proud
of their father
ashton kutcher thank you very much
good night
thank you
keep it going for the reason mike pence
says we have hurricanes
[Laughter]
[Applause]
you look like the little man on top of a
wedding cake that a bakery would refuse
to make for you
will and grace was really the best you
could do it just
[Applause]
just jack just jack is uh it's also what
i'm gonna do in my hotel room alone
after sitting next to blake griffin all
night jesus christ
you're so hot what the
you're so i'd you in front of my
grandparents i that's how
i almost want to you know i feel like
mimi would be proud
blake you look like a black guy that got
made by a printer running out of
ink that's
yeah chris redd is here because comedy
central wasn't sure if blake was black
or not
you look great chris uh you always
dressed like a nine-year-old who just
found a thousand dollars on the sidewalk
robert de niro is here
looking like alf uh
i can't even believe i i get to share
this stage with you tonight robert
deniro and by this stage i mean the
final one of your life it's
sorry i don't feel right about any of
this
caitlyn jenner i just want to thank you
for all you've done for the trans
movement in the size 16 stiletto
industry
you are such an incredible athlete
people forget just how
fast you once ran from your first family
to go be on a reality show
seriously though i know being a new mom
is hard
but even casey anthony knows the current
location of her daughter
okay thank you
you're a republican i don't know why
you've already gained control over a
woman's body
what does that party have to do to lose
your support um
be your son
caitlyn i know you've only publicly
identified as a woman for a few years
but i just want you know that
i know that deep down you have always
been a
and uh
i spell it with a k though for you
you're great thank you you're great
alec baldwin what an honor to be here
roasting justin bieber's wife's oldest
fattest uncle
it's like
i'll never forget that voicemail um that
when you called your daughter
ireland a a thoughtless little pig um
it's gotta be one of the worst things
you can call your daughter after ireland
actually that's that name
yikes speaking of terrible names your
wife's name is hilaria
is it hilarious it's hilarious
oh it's so stupid okay
it doesn't matter she's so hot dude
she's so hot
and fit does getting screamed at burn
calories
you have four kids under the age of six
i just how do you do it i mean isn't
your semen just oatmeal at this point
oh robert just got excited when i said
oatmeal he started salivating
your night nurse is warming it up
backstage it'll be ready in the break
i'm such a fan of the baldwins i've
never been so sure that
four people have buried a hooker
together
alex thank you so much for having me
here tonight thank you
[Applause]
[Music]